const Food0=[
  { question:'What is the main ingredient used to make hummus?',
    rightAnswer:'Chickpeas',
    answers:["Tahini","Humms","Chickpeas","Navy Beans"],
}
,
{ question:'Which famous soft drink was invented in 1892?',
    rightAnswer:'Coca Cola',
    answers:["Coca Cola","Pepsi","Surge","Fanta"],
}
,
{ question:'Which is the only food that can never go off or go bad?',
    rightAnswer:'Honey',
    answers:["Honey","Twinkies","Peanuts","Canned Tuna"],
}
,
{ question:'What popular Mexican dish literally translates as ‘little donkey’?',
    rightAnswer:'Burrito',
    answers:["Burrito","Enchilladas","Frijoles","Taco"],
}
,
{ question:'How many herbs and spices make up the KFC spice blend?',
    rightAnswer:'11',
    answers:["7","9","11","15"],
}
,
{ question:'What is Japanese Sake made from?',
    rightAnswer:'Rice',
    answers:["Rice","Barley","Wheat","Wasabi"],
}

  ]


  const States1=[
    { question:'What is the capital of Washington state?',
      rightAnswer:'Olympia',
      answers:["Olympia","Seattle","Tacoma","Renton"],
  }
  ,
  { question:'What is the only state flag that is two-sided?',
      rightAnswer:'Oregon',
      answers:["Oregon","Texas","New Jersey","North Dakota"],
  }
  ,
  { question:'Which state is known as the “granite state”?',
      rightAnswer:'New Hampshire',
      answers:["New Hampshire","Montana","Oklohoma","Wisconsin"],
  }
  ,
  { question:'Which U.S. state is nicknamed both the “Constitution State” and the “Nutmeg State”?',
      rightAnswer:'Connecticut',
      answers:["Connecticut","Massachesets","Delaware","Vermont"],
  }
  ,
  { question:'What state has the longest freshwater shoreline?',
      rightAnswer:'Michigan',
      answers:["Michigan","Florida","Maine","Minnisota"],
  }
  ,
  { question:'What is the biggest US state in terms of land area?',
      rightAnswer:'Alaska',
      answers:["Alaska","Texas","Ohio","Canada"],
  }
  
    ]
    const Potter2=[
      { question:'Who won the quidditch world cup in Goblet of Fire?',
        rightAnswer:'Bulgaria',
        answers:["Gryffindor","Ireland","Bulgaria","Chuddley Cannons"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'What magical item contains white and red smoke and reacts to a user if they forget something',
        rightAnswer:'Remembrall',
        answers:["Remembrall","Forget-me-not","Snitch","Pensieve"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'What are the names of the three Peverell brothers?',
        rightAnswer:'Antioch, Cadmus and Ignotus',
        answers:["Antioch, Cadmus and Ignotus","Remus, Sirius and James","Alastor, Romulus and Wulfric","Asmodayis, Sybil and Nymphadora"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'How much does a ticket on the Knight Bus cost if it includes hot chocolate?',
        rightAnswer:'14 Sickles',
        answers:["14 Sickles","10 Sickles, 3 Knuts","1 Galleon","7 Sickles"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'What is Rita Skeeter’s animagus form?',
        rightAnswer:'A beetle',
        answers:["A beetle","A Bumblebee","A cat","A mouse"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'Who is the Slytherin house ghost?',
        rightAnswer:'Bloody Baron',
        answers:["Bloody Baron","Peeves","Nearly-Headless Nick","They Grey Lady"],
    }
    
      ]

    const Avatar3=[
      { question:'What is the Order of the Avatar Cycle?(Avatar the Last Airbender)',
        rightAnswer:'Fire, Air, Water, Earth',
        answers:["Fire, Air, Water, Earth","Water, Air, Earth, Fire","Earth, Air, Water, Fire","Fire, Water, Earth, Air"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'Who Started the Tradition of Hunting Dragons for Glory?',
        rightAnswer:'Fire Lord Sozin',
        answers:["Fire Lord Azulon","Fire Lord Sozin","Fire Lord Ozai","Fire Lord Iroh"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'Finish the tune: "Two lovers, forbidden from one another..."',
        rightAnswer:'...war divides their people',
        answers:["...war divides their people","...secret tunnel, secret tunnel","...through the mountains they go","destined to be together"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'What is the name of Rokus earthbending master and how does Roku describe him?',
        rightAnswer:'Sud; Uncompromising, stubborn, and blunt and a lifelong friend.',
        answers:["Sud; Uncompromising, stubborn, and blunt and a lifelong friend.","Ren; Uncompromising, stubborn, and blunt and a lifelong friend.","Wei; Determined, robust, and blunt and a lifelong friend.","Sud; Determined, robust, and blunt and a lifelong friend."],
    }
    ,
    { question:'What is the name of the sinister spirit also known as "the face stealer?"',
        rightAnswer:'Koh',
        answers:["Koh","La","Wa Shi Tong","Tui"],
    }
    ,
    { question:'How many years was Aang trapped in the iceberg ?',
        rightAnswer:'100',
        answers:["100","1","50","200"],
    }
    
      ]
      const Naruto4=[
        { question:'Name the character that can only use Taijutsu?',
          rightAnswer:'Rock Lee',
          answers:["Sakura","Ten Ten","Rock Lee","Sia"],
      }
      ,
      { question:'Name the First Hokage',
          rightAnswer:'Hashirama Senju',
          answers:["Hashirama Senju","Tobyrama Senju","Madara Uchiha","Gaara"],
      }
      ,
      { question:'Whom did Kakashi get his eye from?',
          rightAnswer:'Obito',
          answers:["Obito","Madara","No-one","Danzo"],
      }
      ,
      { question:'Which Akatsuki member launched an attack on the Hidden Leaf Village that led to the death of the 3rd Hokage?',
          rightAnswer:'Orochimaru',
          answers:["Orochimaru","Pain","Itachi","Kissame"],
      }
      ,
      { question:'What does the symbol on Gaaras forehead mean?',
          rightAnswer:'Love',
          answers:["Love","Pain","1Sealing","Three tails"],
      }
      ,
      { question:'Name the fifth Hokage',
          rightAnswer:'Tsunade',
          answers:["Tsunade","Naruto","Itachi","Kakashi"],
      }
      
        ]
        const TV5=[
          { question:'This famous tv show has yellow charaters',
            rightAnswer:'Simpsons',
            answers:["Simpsons","Family Guy","American Dad","Bobs Burgers"],
        }
        ,
        { question:'What breed is the dog Snoopy from the popular TV show/cartoon, The Peanuts?',
            rightAnswer:'Beagle',
            answers:["Beagle","Greyhound","Corgi","Jack Russel Terrier"],
        }
        ,
        { question:'What show follows a city goverment department in Pawnee, Indiana',
            rightAnswer:'Parks',
            answers:["The Office","Parks and Rec","The West Wing","Sewage: A look behind the curtain"],
        }
        ,
        { question:'Who lives in a Pineapple under the sea?',
            rightAnswer:'Spongebob Squarepants',
            answers:["Spongebob Squarepants","Spongebob RoundShirt","Patrick Star","Mr. Krabs"],
        }
        ,
        { question:'What city does the office take place in?',
            rightAnswer:'Scranton',
            answers:["Scranton","Erie","Dallas","Trenton"],
        }
        ,
        { question:'Where finction city does Larulie and Rory live in',
            rightAnswer:'Stars Hollow',
            answers:["Sleepy Hollow","Stars Hollow","Breakingride","Bridgeton"],
        }
        
          ]
      

// this function takes in the catagory number and the question number and return the object within the array
function getQuestionsAndAnswers(cat,qNumber){
  if(cat === 0){
    shuffle(Food0[qNumber].answers)
    return Food0[qNumber]
  }else if(cat === 1){
    shuffle(States1[qNumber].answers)
    return States1[qNumber]
  }else if(cat === 2){
    shuffle(Potter2[qNumber].answers)
    return Potter2[qNumber]
  }else if(cat === 3){
    shuffle(Avatar3[qNumber].answers)
    return Avatar3[qNumber]
  }else if(cat === 4){
    shuffle(Naruto4[qNumber].answers)
    return Naruto4[qNumber]
  }else if(cat === 5){
    shuffle(TV5[qNumber].answers)
    return TV5[qNumber]
  }

  function shuffle(array) {
    array.sort(() => Math.random() - 0.5);
    //console.log(array)
  }

//shuffle(Question0.answers)

}
export{
  getQuestionsAndAnswers
}